utahrealestate.com 2011-12-31

# UtahRealEstate.com | WFR Multiple Listing Service

##  **Utahrealestate.com  
Website Privacy Policy**  

This website ("Website") is owned and operated by the Wasatach Front Regional Multiple Listing Service, Inc. ("WFRMLS" or "We"). We are fully committed to the protection and security of any information that you provide to us as users ("Users") of the Website. We want you to know that we respect and will protect your privacy, so you can enjoy using our service which allows us to better serve your needs.

The Privacy Policy for the Website discloses our approach to privacy and how your personal information is collected and used. Your use of our Website constitutes your acceptance of this Privacy Policy and your consent to the practices it describes. This Privacy Policy only applies to the website. Your visit to this site is subject to both this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use posted elsewhere on the Website.

_THE INFORMATION WFRMLS COLLECTS ABOUT YOU AND HOW IT IS USED_

Generally speaking, the Website is informational. We do not collect any personally identifiable information unless you voluntarily provide it, such as when you submit a request for a real estate agent to contact your, or request any agent's free forms, or when you sign up for new listings or updates from us via email.

As is the case when you visit most websites, to administer our site, your visit triggers the automatic logging of certain anonymous information about your computer system such as the type of browser you use, the server name and your "IP" (Internet Protocol) address. When your web browser or email application requests a web page or email from another computer using the Internet, it automatically gives that computer the "address" where it should send the information. This is called your computer's "IP address." This address does not contain any personally identifiable information.

WFRMLS gathers certain usage information from the Website. This includes the number and frequency of visitors to the Website, number of listings viewed, length of stay, and other statistical information.

We also want our Users to know that we take the security of your information seriously and that we take appropriate measures to protect the files in our data system. We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to guard your nonpublic personal information.

Our Users should know, however, that due to the open communication nature of the Internet we cannot guarantee that communication between you and us, and between us and you, will be free from unauthorized access by third parties nor can we be responsible for information stolen from our servers or computer systems by information harvesting software which may have the ability to scrape data. WFRMLS employs modern technology and safeguards to make reasonable efforts to prevent such practices.

_HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION_

When we ask you for information, we tell you, or it will be clear, why we need any personally identifying information from you either to fulfill a request from you or to provide information or services to you, such as when you submit a request for an agent's free forms, request an agent to contact you, or when you sign up for emails containing listings you desire or other services delivered electronically from us to you. YOU CAN ALWAYS REFUSE TO PROVIDE PERSONAL INFORMATION, BUT THIS MAY RESULT IN DECREASED FUNCTIONALITY OF THE WEBSITE FOR YOU.

_WE DO NOT SELL OR RENT YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION_

Any information collected by WFRMLS in connection with your use of the Website will belong exclusively to WFRMLS.

As a matter of policy, aside from our own use of your personal information, WFRMLS will not sell, share, or rent information about you or your business with any unaffiliated third parties. We may, however, have to disclose, transfer, sell or assign your information obtained through the Website, or otherwise in our possession, to a third party as a result of the following:

  * If you consent to such disclosure. For instance, when you indicate you want WFRMLS to provide you or a related party with WFRMLS or products or services.

  * We may disclose such information to companies and individuals we employ or engage to perform services on our behalf, such as analyzing data, maintaining our servers, or hosting the Website. These companies and individuals will only have access to your information to the extent necessary to perform their functions.

  * We may disclose information to the government, law enforcement, or third parties when WFRMLS, in its sole discretion, believes it is necessary in connection with activity that is illegal or may expose us, or you, to liability or to protect us, you, or the public.

  * WFRMLS may disclose and transfer such information to a third party who acquires all or substantially all of WFRMLS's business or operations.

_WE WANT TO PROVIDE ONLY INFORMATION YOU WANT_

As a User, you control what marketing information you receive from us, by simply letting us know if you wish to opt out and not receive information from us. If you do not wish to receive information from us, you should check the particular communication or the corresponding sections of our website for opt-out instructions.

_COOKIE TECHNOLOGY_

WFRMLS employs cookies to recall information that you provide, and so that you can customize certain portions of the website for your own purposes. Cookies help us keep track of the pages that you visit while on our Website. In case you did not know, "cookies" are small text files sent by Web servers to be stored on the computers of website users. These files often contain personalization settings or unique identifiers to keep track of your information and to help us understand the movements of users within and between websites. Cookies may contain personal information, like email addresses, usernames, passwords, or completely anonymous information, like a randomly generated number. They may be deleted once you leave a website, or close the web browser; or they may remain so that the website remembers you the next time you visit that site. Most browsers allow you to decline cookies automatically or to accept or decline each cookie individually. If you decline cookies from the Website, you may not be able to use some sections or the Website or it may hinder their function.

_PRIVACY STATEMENT CHANGES_

We reserve the right to change or amend our Privacy Policy to address new issues of privacy and information security and to reflect changes to our Website or business practices. Each version of this policy may be identified by its effective date which is located at the top of the page. Your continued use of the Website constitutes your acceptance of the revised Privacy Policy.

_FORUMS_

The Website may include discussion forums (such as message boards and chat rooms) that enable Users to communicate with each other. WFRMLS is under no obligation to moderate or edit the forums, and will not be responsible for the content or use of any material posted on any forum on the Website. WFRMLS retains the right to delete at any time and for any or no reason any material posted on the Website.

_QUESTIONS ABOUT OUR PRIVACY AND INFORMATION SECURITY PRACTICES?_

If you have any questions about our privacy practices or procedures, or if you want to revise, update, correct, or change any information you provide to WFRMLS, please feel free to contact us at:

     Wasatch Front Regional Multiple Listing Service, Inc.
     230 West Towne Ridge Parkway, Suite 400
     Sandy, Utah 84070
     (801) 676-5400
     privacy@wfrmls.com
